Guide to the Stereograph File [1855-1964] (Bulk 1860-1900) PR 65
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
  - New York--Lake George--Fort William Henry Hotel, [ca. 1865-188-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Lake Mahopac, [187-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Lake Mohunk, [ca. 187--ca. 188-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Le Roy, [187-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Little Falls, [187-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Lockport, [186-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Luzerne, [187-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Middletown, [186-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Mortonville, [187-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Mount Lebanon, [ca. 1869-187-] (Box 25)
  - New York--Mount McGregor, [ca. 1884] (Box 25)
  - New York--Mount Vernon, 1959 1961 (Box 25)
  - New York--Mumford, [188-] (Box 25)
  - New York--New Rochelle, [186-] (Box 26)
  - New York--Newburgh, [186--ca. 1900] (Box 26)
  - New York--NYC--New York Stereoscope Views [Set], [190-] (Box 26)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Alexander Hamilton, 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Broadway, 1953-1963 (Box 26)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Brooklyn, [ca. 1883-1959] (Box 26)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Brooklyn, Construction, [ca. 1870-ca. 1883] (Box 26)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Brooklyn, scenes on, [ca. 1883-1950] (Box 26)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- George Washington, 1933-1954 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Harlem River, [ca. 1873] (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Harlem River R.R., [ca. 1880] (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Henry Hudson Parkway, 1954 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- High Bridge, [ca. 1959-1963] (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- MacComb's Dam, 2nd, 1870 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Manhattan, [ca. 1950-1959] (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Queensboro, 1908-1958 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Triborough, 1954 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Wards Island, 1956 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Washington, [ca. 1890-1957] (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Bridges -- Williamsburg, 1903-1959 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Tunnels, [194--1960] (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Harbor -- General, 1859-1899 (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Harbor -- Battery, [1859-191-] (Box 27)
  - New York--NYC--Harbor -- Celebrations, 1859-1898 (Box 28)
  - New York--NYC--Harbor -- Ferry terminals and slips, 1859-1959 (Box 28)
  - New York--NYC--Harbor -- Piers, wharves, 1859-1957 (Box 28)
  - New York--NYC--Harbor -- Steamboats, [ca. 1859-ca. 1880] (Box 28)
  - New York--NYC--Rivers -- East River, [ca. 1859-ca. 1890] (Box 28)
  - New York--NYC--Rivers -- Harlem River & Ship Canal, [ca. 1870-1958] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC--Rivers -- Hudson or North, [ca. 1870-1900] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--From the water, [186--1964] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Panoramic views, [ca. 1865-1957] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Air terminals, 1953-1955 (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Bus terminals, 1953-1963 (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Subways, [ca. 1870-1963] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Baptist, [ca. 1863-1952] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Buddhist temple, 1954 (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Catholic (Roman), [ca. 1870-1963] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Congregational, [ca. 1875] (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Dutch Reformed, 1857-1959 (Box 29)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Friends (Quaker), [ca. 1860] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Jewish Synagogues, [ca. 187--1961] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Methodist, [ca. 186--187-] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Orthodox, Greek/Russian, 1957-1959 (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Presbyterian, [ca. 1865-1950] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Protestant Episcopal, [ca. 1865-1958] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Unitarian, [ca. 1858-187-?] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Churches -- Universalist, [ca. 1870] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Clubs, Organizations, [ca. 1868-1956] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Clubs, Organizations - Tammany Hall, [1868-188-] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs., [189--1962] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Banks, [ca, 1867-1962] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Commodities exchanges, [187--1954] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Drug stores, [ca. 1868-187-] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Hotels, [ca. 1865-1957] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Hotels -- Fifth Avenue, [ca. 1865-ca. 1895] (Box 30)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Hotels -- Grand Central, [ca. 1865-188-] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Hotels -- Grand Union, [ca. 1874-188-] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Insurance buildings, [ca. 1875-1954] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Markets, [ca. 1875-1956] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Photography studios, [ca. 1859] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Publishing, [ca. 1865-1954] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Restaurants and taverns, [ca. 1870-1963] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Shops, exteriors, [186--1957] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Shops, interiors, [186--188-] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Stock exchanges, [ca. 1870-196-] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Empire State, 1954-1957 (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Flatiron Building, [190--1925] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Western Union Building, [187--188-] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Commercial bldgs. -- Woolworth Building, [ca. 1913-ca. 194-] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs., [ca. 1870-1960] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Castle Clinton, [ca. 1865-ca. 1915] (Box 31)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- City Hall, [185--1954] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Forts, not Clinton, [ca. 1865-188-] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Hall of Records, [ca. 1865-1925] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Hospitals, [185--1963] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Institutions, 1861-1951 (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Post Office, Broadway, [ca. 1869-189-] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Post Office, Nassau St., [186-] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Tombs, Old, [ca. 1865-1896] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- Treasury, [ca. 1860-1951] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Gov't and Public Bldgs. -- United Nations, 1951-1954 (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Libraries, [ca. 1865- 1963] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Museums, [ca. 1865-1961] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Museums -- Barnum's, [1868-187-] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Museums -- Cloisters, 1949 (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Museums -- Guggenheim, 1958-1961 (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Museums -- Metropolitan, [ca. 187--1961] (Box 32)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Museums -- Museum of the City of New York, 1958 (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Museums -- New-York Historical Society, [ca. 1865-1961] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Residences -- Apartment houses, [ca. 1884-1960] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Residences -- Houses and homes, exterior, [ca. 186--1957] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Residences -- Houses and homes, interior, [ca. 1860-188-] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Schools & colleges, [ca. 1865-1961] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Schools & colleges -- City College of N.Y., 1927-1952 (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Schools & colleges -- Cooper Institute, [ca. 1865-188-] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Schools & colleges -- National Academy of Design, [ca. 1865-188-] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Schools & colleges -- New York University, [ca. 1870-1957] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Theaters, [ca. 1865-1964] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Theaters -- Academy of Music, [ca. 1870] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Theaters -- Booth's, [ca. 1868-ca. 1875] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Theaters -- Central Park Gardens, [ca. 1870] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Theaters -- Grand Opera House, [ca. 1865-1960] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Theaters -- Niblo's, [ca. 1860-ca. 187-] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Monuments and statues, 1953-1956 (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Monuments and statues -- Grant's Tomb, 1897-1925 (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Monuments and statues -- Statue of Liberty, [ca. 1900-1959] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Monuments and statues -- Worth Monument, [1860-189-] (Box 33)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares, [189--1963] (Box 34)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Bowling Green, 1865-1962 (Box 34)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Bryant Park (Reservoir Sq.), [ca. 1871-188-] (Box 34)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Arbors, [ca. 1863-ca. 1900] (Box 34)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Bridges, [1860-189-] (Box 34)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Children, [186--188-] (Box 35)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Events & sports, [ca. 1862-ca. 1900] (Box 35)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Fountains, [1863-188-] (Box 35)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Goat Carts, [ca. 1870-1891] (Box 35)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Horses/carriage, [ca. 1870-ca. 1910] (Box 35)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Ice Skating, [ca. 1863-ca. 189-] (Box 35)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Lakes & ponds, [ca. 1860-1957] (Box 35)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Mall, [1863-188-] (Box 36)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Menagerie, [1863--ca. 1900] (Box 36)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Miscellaneous, [ca. 1865-1901] (Box 36)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Mt. St. Vincent, [1863-] (Box 36)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Paths, 1863-1896 (Box 36)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Ramble, [ca. 1860-189-] (Box 36)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Statuary, 1863-1961 (Box 37)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Structures, [ca. 1860-1956] (Box 37)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park -- Terrace, [ca. 1862-ca. 1905] (Box 37)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Central Park, by Thompson, 1860-1862 (Box 37)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Chatham Square, [186-] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Jones Wood, [ca. 1865-ca. 1875] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Madison Square, [ca. 1876-1951] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Times Square, 1940-1963 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Union Square, [187--189-] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Parks & Squares -- Washington Square, [187--1957] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 14th, [ca. 1870-ca. 1905] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 19th, 1958 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 22nd, [ca, 1870] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 23rd, [ca. 1870] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 32nd, 1958 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 34th, [ca. 1870-1953] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 35th, 1958 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 42nd, 1949-1957 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 49th, 1959 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 52nd, 1957 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 54th, 1956 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets --57th, [ca. 1870-1959] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 58th, [ca. 1865] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 69th, 1963 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 125th Street, undated (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 204th Street, 1953 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- 207th, 1953 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Ardlea Court, 1953 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Beekman Place, 1961 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Beekman Street, [ca. 1870] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Bleeker, 1957 (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Bowery, [ca. 1885-1905] (Box 38)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broad Street, [ca. 1865-1960] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, below Wall, [ca. 1865-1962] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Wall - Fulton, [ca. 1859-1962] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Fulton - Chambers, 1865-1960 (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Chambers - Canal Street, [ca. 1865-ca. 1880] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Canal - Grand, [ca. 1865-ca. 1900] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Grand-Broome, [ca. 1868] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Broome-Spring, [ca. 1865-1964] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Spring-Prince, [186-] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Prince - Houston, 1859-1894 (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Houston - Fourth, [ca. 1865-189-] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Fourth - Fourteenth, [ca. 1860-190-] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Fourteenth - Twenty-third, [ca. 1870-190-] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Twenty-third - twenty-ninth, [ca. 1870] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Twenty-ninth - forty-seventh, [ca. 1880-1955] (Box 39)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Broadway, Forty-seventh - 242nd, 1940-1962 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Canal, [ca. 1870-1959] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Cedar, 1958 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Central Park South, 1957 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Central Park West, 1961 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Chambers, [ca. 1885] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Cortlandt, undated (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Elizabeth, 1902 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- FDR, or East River, Drive, 1956 1958 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Five Points, 1865 1956 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Gay Street, 1954 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Gold Street, 1959 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Gramercy Park West, 1953-1954 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Greenwich Street, [ca. 1865-1953] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Hudson, 1962 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Lafayette, 1866-1954 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Little West Twelfth, 1954 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- MacDougal, 1955 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Mott, 1951 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Nassau, [ca. 1890] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Park Place, [ca. 1865-ca. 1880] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Park Row, [ca. 1859-1954] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Pearl, 1959 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Pomander Walk, 1955 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Riverside Drive, 1933 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- South, [ca. 1865-1957] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- State, 1910 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Sutton Place, 1956 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Wall, [ca. 1865-1909] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Waverly Place, 1957 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- West, [ca. 1870-ca. 1900] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- West Side Highway, 1954 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- Whitehall, [ca. 1858-1959] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets -- William, 1953 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Third, 1954-1964 (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Fourth, [ca. 1861-ca. 1870] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Fifth, 14th - 34th, [ca. 1865-1953] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Fifth, 34th - 42nd, [ca.. 1860-ca. 1935] (Box 40)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Fifth, 42nd - 59th, [ca. 1865-1959] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Fifth, above 59th, [ca. 1870-1962] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Sixth, [ca. 1900-1962] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Seventh, [ca. 1940] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Eighth, 1957 (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Ninth, 1940-1958 (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Amsterdam, 1956 (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Lexington, 1872-1959 (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Madison, 1956 (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Park, [ca. 1865-1961] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Streets, Avenues -- Vanderbilt, 1959 (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, [ca. 1870-1933] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads -- Depots, [ca. 1867-ca. 1871] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads -- Depots -- Grand Central, 1871, [ca. 1870-188-] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads -- Depots -- Grand Central, 1913, 1925-1957 (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads -- Depots -- Pennsylvania Station, [193--1957] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, Elevated, [ca. 1878-1957] (Box 41)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, Elevated -- Stations, [ca. 1880-1955] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, Elevated -- Third Avenue Line, [ca. 1880-1955] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, Elevated -- Sixth Avenue Line, [ca. 1885-ca. 1900] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, Elevated -- Battery Park, [ca. 188-] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, Elevated -- Chatham Square, [187--188-] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, elevated -- Coenties Slip, [188--190-] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Railroads, elevated -- Northern Manhattan, [188--1940] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Advertising, [ca. 1870-ca. 189-] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Architectural details, 1953 1962 (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Balloons, [186-] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Building construction, [ca. 1907-1961] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Chinatown, 1925-1951 (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Fairs and Festivals, 1951 (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Fairs and festivals -- American Institute, [ca. 1870] (Box 42)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Fairs and festivals -- Metropolitan Sanitary Fair, 1864 (Box 43)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Fairs and festivals -- World's Fair, 1939 (Box 43)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Fire fighting, [1859 - ca. 1870] (Box 43)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Harlem, [192-] (Box 43)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Holiday decorations, 1953-1963 (Box 43)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Immigration, [ca. 1880 - ca. 1920] (Box 43)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Lower East Side, [ca. 1900 - 1905] (Box 43)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, 1859-1900 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, Japanese Embassy, 1861, 1860 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, Lincoln's funeral, 1865 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, Labor Day, 1887 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, Centennial, 1889 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, Columbus, 1892 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, Dewey, 1899 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Parades, World War I, 1919 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Police, [ca. 1900] (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Shanties, [ca. 1870] (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Sidewalk activities, 1932-1952 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Television, 1940-1962 (Box 44)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Turkish baths, [ca. 1890] (Box 45)
  - New York--NYC -- Manhattan--Topics -- Window displays, 1940-1964 (Box 45)
  - New York--NYC -- Brooklyn, [ca. 1860-1953] (Box 45)
  - New York--NYC -- Brooklyn--Brooklyn Navy Yard, [ca. 1860-1898] (Box 45)
  - New York--NYC -- Brooklyn--Coney Island, [ca. 1870-1925] (Box 45)
  - New York--NYC -- Brooklyn--Green-wood Cemetery, [ca. 1865-ca. 1885] (Box 45)
  - New York--NYC -- Brooklyn--Prospect Park, [ca. 187--ca. 188-] (Box 45)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx, [ca. 1865-1959] (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Bronx River, [ca. 1865-ca. 1900] (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Churches and shrines, 1954-1961 (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Houses and homes, 1873-1963 (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Parks, [ca. 1900-1961] (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Railroads and subways, [ca. 1875-1962] (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Schools and colleges, [ca. 1885-1961] (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Statues and monuments, [ca. 1885-1956] (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Streets, 1948-1861 (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--Streets -- Cross Bronx Expressway, 1958-1963 (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Bronx--City Island, 1961-1962 (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Queens, [ca. 1870-1951] (Box 46)
  - New York--NYC -- Staten Island, [185--186-] (Box 46)
  - New York--Niagara Falls--Falls, [ca. 1856-ca. 1930] (Box 47)
  - New York--Niagara Falls--Boats, [ca. 1870-ca. 1900] (Box 47)
  - New York--Niagara Falls--Bridges, [ca. 1856-1913] (Box 47)
  - New York--Niagara Falls--Buildings and towers, [ca. 1856-ca. 1885] (Box 48)
  - New York--Niagara Falls--People, [ca. 1856-ca. 1930] (Box 48)